Jason Mason

Hospitable Front of House Shift Leader leverages interpersonal and communication skills to lead, influence, and encourage staff and deliver outstanding experiences for guests. Seeking to utilize my 3 years of customer service and managerial experience to provide an optimistic workplace and excellent customer care.

11439 Lost Mine Trail
San Antonio, TX 78245
(210) 418-9836
Jasonmason96@Yahoo.com

EXPERIENCE

Singh's Vietnamese - Front of House Shift Leader San Antonio, TX | 11/2017 - 05/2020

- Drove excellent customer service through coaching, role modeling and incorporating customer feedback to reinforce and improve quality of service.
- Handled complaints, settled disputes and resolved grievances to maintain customer satisfaction.
- Managed day-to-day FOH operations to drive quality standards and exceed customer expectations.
- Demonstrated leadership by keeping up with cleanliness and organization and delegating roles to employees.
- Helped create the training program for new employees and current ones.
- Ordered, managed, and restocked new and current inventory.

Target - Softlines Team Member

San Antonio, TX | July 2017 - October 2017

- Provided excellent customer service and alerted guests to upcoming sales events and promotions.
- Stocked and replenished merchandise according to store merchandising layouts.
- Cleaned and organized the store, including the checkout desk and displays.
- Operated the POS for cash, check and credit card transactions.

SKILLS

Team Building

Staff Management

Training and mentoring

Customer Service

Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Powerpoint)

Average Typing Speed: 65.47WPM

EDUCATION

The University of Texas at San Antonio

San Antonio, TX

Public Health Major

August 2016 - August 2019

GPA: 3.5